impulse.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy - Impulse SafeConnect - Network Security

Maintaining the privacy of end users is a primary design consideration and long-term objective of all Impulse products. Please click below for more information specific to our products, as well as for our website, impulse.com.

impulse.com

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from [www.impulse.com](http://www.impulse.com/) and support.impulse.com  (the “Sites”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit one of our Sites, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Sites, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Sites, and information about how you interact with the Sites. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Sites, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Sites.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and other requests made through forms presented through our Sites (e.g.: demo request forms, contact us form, and support incident form).

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use your contact information (including name, email address, phone number, and title) entered in to forms to respond to your specific requests for more information and then to further communicate information that may be of interest to you related to our products and services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us (in particular, your IP address) improve and optimize our Sites (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Sites, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Sites–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Sites’ data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Sites), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Sites, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

MINORS

The Sites is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at sales@impulse.com or by mail using the details provided below:

 **5650 Breckenridge Park Dr #201, Tampa, FL, 33610, United States**

SafeConnect Network Access Control (NAC)

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

This privacy policy explains what information Impulse Point, LLC. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) gathers about individuals that use an Organization’s Network, where access to that Network is managed by Impulse’s SafeConnect™ Network Access Control (NAC) Solution (the “Service”). 

SafeConnect NAC enables organizations to take more proactive measures in ensuring a secure IT infrastructure. The goal is to provide for an environment free of security threats and vulnerabilities—which promotes the exchange of ideas, information, and content to create a positive and productive network environment for all parties.

Each Organization maintains full and complete control over their own policies and how, or even if, these policies are enforced. Each Organization determines their strategy for allowing full access, warnings, quarantines, and remediation.

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

Where we do use your data, we use it to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

 **Definitions**

 **Service**

Service is the SafeConnect NAC and associated client application, known as the Policy key, provided and operated by Impulse Point, LLC.

 **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

 **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).

 **Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.  For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Impulse Point, LLC and your Organization’s SafeConnect administrator are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. ** **

 **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.  We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

 **Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.  With respect to privacy, there are three classes of users of this system:

  *  _Service Administrators:_ Employees of Impulse Point, LLC that support the Service.  Impulse Point LLC. employees do not have access to the data being protected by the Service and will only access the operational data of a specific Organization if provided permission by the organizational administrator.
  *  _Organization Administrators:_ Organizational administrators do not have access to the data being protected by the Service but do have access to the operational data collected by the Service.  If you are an administrator in an Organization using SafeConnect NAC, you will interact with Impulse Point LLC regarding the rights of your Organization and users.
  *  _Individual Users:_ Individual Users that use the Service are required to comply to the network access policies of the Organization providing the SafeConnect NAC managed Network.  If you are a user at an organization subscribing to the Service, you will interact with your organizations SafeConnect NAC administrator regarding your rights. Opting to permit the organization to collect limited personal data may be a stipulation of the Organization to permit access to the Organization’s network.

 **Network**

The Local Area Network whose access is being managed by SafeConnect NAC.  The portion of the Network managed by SafeConnect is based on the policies and configuration provided by the Organization.

 **Organization**

The institution using SafeConnect NAC to manage access to their Network.

 **Information Collection And Use**

The software installed as part of the SafeConnect NAC Solution (i.e., the Policy Key) does not report or log any activity other than what is required to ensure end user compliance with the endpoint security policies set forth by the organization.

No sensitive personal information is collected or stored. In situations where the end user device is found to be out of compliance with stated security policies, the SafeConnect solution will warn or quarantine the endpoint device based on the policies defined by the organization within the SafeConnect Policy Manager.

SafeConnect collects no information until it is configured by the user’s policy administrator. All queries of a user’s device must be explicitly formulated by the organization’s policy administrator before they can be evaluated by SafeConnect. SafeConnect does not gather any personal information, or perform any checks, that is not configured by a policy administrator.

Additionally, SafeConnect has been designed with personal privacy in mind and can only respond to a limited range of true/false questions. These questions center around the health and configuration of the endpoint and the impact it may be having on network performance. The system cannot respond to open-ended questions, or general requests for information. The system can only return a true/false answer and the transaction occurs over an encrypted communications channel. For example, “Is XYZ anti-virus software up to date and running on this device?” The answer is either true or false.

 **Types of Data Collected**

 ** _Personal Data_**

No direct, sensitive Personal Data about an individual is collected.  However, Operational Data related to the use of the Organization’s Network is collected to permit SafeConnect NAC to provide visibility into the use of the Organization’s Network.  The collection of this data is intended to protect both the Network and the users on the Network and thereby help secure Personal Data.

 ** _Operational Data (Usage Data)_**

SafeConnect NAC collects Operational information on how and when the Organization’s Network is accessed (“Operational Data”). This Operational Data includes non-sensitive Personal Data that is limited to your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), MAC address, browser type, browser version, device type (e.g.: Windows versus macOS), the time and date of when you attempted to use the Network, and the time spent on the Network.

 ** _Tracking Cookies Data_**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  **Session Cookies.**  We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  *  **Preference Cookies.**  We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  *  **Security Cookies.**  We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

 **Use of Data**

Impulse Point, LLC. uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide a more personalized experience to our Service
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

 **Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Impulse Point, LLC. legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Impulse Point, LLC. may process your Personal Data because:

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

 **Retention of Data**

In terms of the Operational Data described above, the retention period is controlled by the policies of the Organization using SafeConnect NAC to manage their Network.

For other data collected to support the individuals that work ant the Organization, Impulse Point, LLC. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

 **Transfer of Data**

Personal Data SafeConnect NAC does collect is not transferred outside of the Organization’s Network.

Personal Data you provide for the purpose of interacting with Impulse Point’s Support operations is maintained by a third-party provider, Atlassian.com (https://www.atlassian.com/legal/privacy-policy).

Impulse Point, LLC. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure of Data

 **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Impulse Point, LLC. may be required to disclose the limited Personal Data collected if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

 **Legal Requirements**

Impulse Point, LLC. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Impulse Point, LLC.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

 **Security of Data**

Real-time policy status metrics of endpoint devices under policy management are kept in a secure database within the SafeConnect Policy Enforcer Appliance, which remains on the organization’s premises. The SafeConnect system database contains no information that can link directly back to end user personal content. The data collected is related only to the status of specific policies defined by the organization.

Under certain circumstances end users may be denied Network access and quarantined based on the organization’s acceptable use policy enforcement rules. In such circumstances the system provides remediation guidance to the end user to become compliant with security policy. As always, the data collected is related only to policy status and it is used solely for statistical trending and compliance auditing by the organization.

In short, Impulse will never collect or store personal information from its customer’s constituents and will never communicate directly with end users outside of an Organization’s SafeConnect Managed Network environment.

 ** ** **“Do Not Track” Signals**

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.  You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

 **Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Impulse Point, LLC. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this policy.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  *  **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.**  Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your subscription settings.  If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this policy.
  *  **The right of rectification.**  You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  *  **The right to object.**  You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  *  **The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  *  **The right to data portability.**  You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  *  **The right to withdraw consent.**  You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Impulse Point, LLC. relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

 **Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  At this time third-party Service Providers are limited to Amazon Web Services. We use Amazon Web Services, to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

 **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.  You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email:  sales@impulse.com
  * By visiting this page on our website: https://impulse.com/contact/
  * By phone :  +1 8136072770
  * By mail: _  _5650 Breckenridge Park Dr. Suite #201, Tampa, FL 33610 United States

SafeConnect Software Defined Perimeter (SDP)

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

Impulse Point, LLC. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates SafeConnect SDP (the “Service”), the related website ( _[sdp.cloud.impulse.com](http://sdp.cloud.impulse.com/)_ ), and the SafeConnect SDP client application (installable on Microsoft Windows, Apple’s macOS, Apple’s iOS, and Google’s Android).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

SafeConnect SDP is a service that organizations utilize to protect the security and privacy of data owned by their organization.  The actual data protected by SafeConnect SDP is not made visible by the Service to the administrators, rather only Operational Data collected by the system to help ensure the security and privacy of the data being protected is provided by the Service to the administrators—however, some of that Operational Data collected is of a personal nature, as described below. 

 **Definitions**

 **Service**

Service is the sdp.cloud.impulse.com website and associated client application provided and operated by Impulse Point, LLC.

 **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

 **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).

 **Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.  For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Impulse Point, LLC and your organization’s SafeConnect administrator are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

 **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.  We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

 **Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.  With respect to privacy, there are three classes of users of this system:

Service Administrators: Employees of Impulse Point, LLC that support the Service.  Impulse Point LLC. employees do not have access to the data being protected by the Service and will only access the operational data of a specific organization if provided permission by the organizational administrator.

Organization Administrators: Organizational administrators do not have access to the data being protected by the Service, but do have access to the operational data collected by the Service.  If you are an administrator in an organization using SafeConnect SDP, you will interact with Impulse Point LLC. regarding the rights of your organization and users. 

Individual Users: Individual Users use the Service to have their data or their organizations data protected.  If you are a user at an organization subscribing to the Service, you will interact with your organizations SafeConnect SDP administrator regarding your rights. Opting to permit the organization to collect limited personal data may be a stipulation of the Organization to permit access to the Organization’s private data.

 ** ** **Information Collection And Use**

 ** ** We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

 **Types of Data Collected**

 ** _Personal Data_**

The Personal Data listed below is collected by the marketing portion of the Service and is only collected from the Service Administrator (not Individual Users).  While registering for our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Company name and job role
  * Cookies and Usage Data (see below for more detail)

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with Service support information, educational, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

 ** _Operational Data (Usage Data)_**

We may also collect Operational information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Operational Data”). This Operational Data may also include personal information but is limited to your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other non-personal diagnostic data.

 ** _Tracking Cookies Data_**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are

sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  **Session Cookies.**  We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  *  **Preference Cookies.**  We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  *  **Security Cookies.**  We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

 ** ** **Use of Data**

 ** ** Impulse Point, LLC. uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide a more personalized experience to our Service
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

 **Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Impulse Point, LLC. legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Impulse Point, LLC. may process your Personal Data because:

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

 **Retention of Data**

Impulse Point, LLC. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Impulse Point, LLC. will also retain Operational Data for internal analysis purposes. Operational Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

 **Transfer of Data**

 ** ** Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, here, to the United States and process it here.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Impulse Point, LLC. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

 ** ** **Disclosure of Data**

 ** ** **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Impulse Point, LLC. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

 ** ** **Legal Requirements**

Impulse Point, LLC. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Impulse Point, LLC.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

 ** ** **Security of Data**

The security of all your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **“Do Not Track” Signals**

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.  You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

 **Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Impulse Point, LLC. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this policy.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  *  **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.**  Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your subscription settings.  If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us using the contact information at the end of this policy.
  *  **The right of rectification.**  You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  *  **The right to object.**  You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  *  **The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  *  **The right to data portability.**  You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  *  **The right to withdraw consent.**  You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Impulse Point, LLC. relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

 **Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  At this time third-party Service Providers are limited to Amazon Web Services. We use Amazon Web Services, to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

 ** ** **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.  You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: sales@impulse.com
  * By visiting this page on our website: https://impulse.com/contact/
  * By phone: +1 8136072771
  * By mail: 5650 Breckenridge Park Dr. Suite #201, Tampa, FL 33610 United State

Does the SafeConnect solution collect sensitive personal information?

No. SafeConnect does not gather any information, or perform any checks, that are not configured by a policy administrator. SafeConnect is completely passive until it is configured by the organization’s policy administrator. All queries of a user’s machine must be explicitly formulated by the organization’s policy administrator before they can be evaluated by SafeConnect. Impulse will never collect or store personal information from its customer’s constituents.

What is a Policy Key? 

The SafeConnect Policy Key is a lightweight persistent client agent (less than 1MB in size). The SafeConnect Policy Key certifies that the endpoint device adheres to the specific endpoint security policies of the organization on a continuous/real-time basis.

How do you get a Policy Key?

The Policy Key is downloaded to a new user as part of the device registration process. It can also be pre-distributed via the organization’s software distribution mechanism of choice for managed environments, such as MS SCCM, Zenworks or through active directory group policies.

Can you refuse to have a Policy Key installed on your computer?

Yes. However, the decision on who can, and cannot, access an Organization’s Network remains with the organization that owns and manages the network. Many organizations require that users must read, accept, and adhere to a collection of Acceptable Use Polices (AUP) as a condition of gaining access to the Network. This may include the installation of a policy key. This, of course, is the decision of the Organization.

Does the Policy Key stay on the computer forever?

No. The SafeConnect Policy Key automatically dissolves (uninstalls itself) after a pre-determined time of inactivity. Users can also uninstall the policy key themselves if they choose.

How can I be sure that SafeConnect is not gathering sensitive personal information?

Impulse is committed to protecting the privacy of your Organization and the end user community you support. We have established security, technology, and business processes to ensure that sensitive personal information is never collected or stored by our applications or services.

An independent examination of our privacy practices certifies that Impulse and the SafeConnect solution both conform to the American Institute of CPAs (AICPA) standards. The completion of a Service Organization Controls – Type 2 (SOC 2) Privacy Report resulted in an independent CPA firm finding that Impulse’s Privacy Statement is accurate.
